<?xml version="1.0"?>
<errors>
	<error id="10">
		<title>Can't plot zero or subzero values on a logarithmic axis</title>
		<description>
			This error occurs in the following situations:
			<ul>
				<li>If a zero or subzero data value is added to a logarithmic axis</li>
				<li>If the minimum of a logarithimic axis is set to 0 or less</li>
				<li>If the threshold is set to 0 or less</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="13">
		<title>Rendering div not found</title>
		<description>
			This error occurs if the <a href="http://www.highcharts.com/ref/#chart--renderTo">chart.renderTo</a> 
			option is misconfugured so that Highcharts is unable to find the HTML element to render the chart in.
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="14">
		<title>String value sent to series.data, expected Number</title>
		<description>
			<p>This happens if you pass in a string as a data point, for example in a setup like this:</p>
			<pre>series: [{
	data: ["3", "5", "1", "6"]
}]</pre>
			<p>Highcharts expects the data values to be numbers. The most common reason for this is that data is parsed
				from CSV or from a XML source, and the implementer forgot to run <code>parseFloat</code> on the 
				parsed value.</p>
				
				
			<p>For performance reasons internal type casting is not performed,
			and only the first value is checked (since 2.3).</p> 
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="15">
		<title>Highcharts expects data to be sorted</title>
		<description>
			<p>This happens when you are trying to create a line series or a stock chart where the data is not
				sorted in ascending X order. For performance reasons, Highcharts does not sort the data,
				instead it is required that the implementer pre-sorts the data.</p> 
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="16">
		<title>Highcharts already defined in the page</title>
		<description>
			<p>This error happens the second time Highcharts or Highstock is loaded in the same page, so the <code>Highcharts</code>
			namespace is already defined. Keep in mind that the <code>Highcharts.Chart</code> constructor and all features
			of Highcharts are included in Highstock, so if you are running <code>Chart</code> and <code>StockChart</code> in combination, you 
			only need to load the highstock.js file. </p> 
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="17">
		<title>The requested series type does not exist</title>
		<description>
			<p>This error happens when you are setting <code>chart.type</code> or <code>series.type</code> to a series type
			this isn't defined in Highcharts. A typical reason may be that your are missing the extension file where the serires type
			is defined, for example in order to run an <code>arearange</code> series you need to load the <code>highcharts-more.js</code>
			file.</p> 
		</description>
	</error>
	<error id="18">
		<title>The requested axis does not exist</title>
		<description>
			<p>This error happens when you set a series' <code>xAxis</code> or <code>yAxis</code> property to point to an axis that does not exist.</p> 
		</description>
	</error>
</errors>
